cineversity.com 2019-07-08

# Cineversity - Cinema 4D Training and Tools

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide to Maxon Computer, Inc. when you visit, or use our products or services located on Cineversity ([www.cineversity.com](http://www.cineversity.com/)), and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing such information. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect: (i) through our Services, and (ii) in electronic messages between you and our Services.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other Maxon Computer, Inc. services or any information collected by us offline or via third-party sites that may be accessed through hyperlinks on our services.

By accessing or using our Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you have any concern about providing information to us or having such information used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy, you should not visit our website, apps or otherwise use our services. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS OR USE OUR SERVICES.

We collect several types of information about visitors and/or users of our services. We may collect this information either directly when you provide it to us or automatically as you navigate through Cineversity. This information includes:

  * We will collect and process your personal data when you register for and create an account, subscribe to a newsletter, submit feedback, enter a contest, fill out a survey, post in a forum, send us a communication, or otherwise engage with the website. 

  * When ordering products or services on Cineversity, you may also be asked to provide a credit card number and other payment-related information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is required to use the services (e.g. registering an account, subscribing to a premium membership, etc.) and some is voluntary. If you do not provide data when needed for a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

  * We collect your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers and/or software, to administer our services, and to gather demographic information.

  * We may collect certain information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. Such information tells us about your equipment, browsing actions, and the resources that you access and use through the services, such as your operating system and browser type. We use analytics and similar services, to help us to deliver a better and more personalized service to users by enabling us to estimate and track usage patterns, customize our services according to your individual preferences, and speed up your searches.

  * When you use our services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use and the operating system version, so we know the best version of the application to provide you. We do not ask you for, access, or track any location-based information from your mobile device at any time while using our services.

  * When you contact us for customer support we may collect additional information to resolve your issue.

  * We are not a site targeted at children or those under the age of 13. If you are a school and you use a Cineversity service for children under the age of 13, or the equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, you are responsible for obtaining consent from the parents/legal guardians of each child you wish to allow to participate in using any of our services. A child using our services will be able to participate in certain limited activities (such as taking online educational and informational courses).

By submitting your personal data, you agree to the transfer, storing and processing of your data outside of the country where you reside. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Cineversity plugins do not have access to, make use of or store any personal data. Specifically, the CV-AR App makes use of the True Depth camera to capture your face structure, facial movement, images and sound. This data is stored locally on your iPhone. Cineversity does not have access to, or use, this data in any way. You can transfer the data to your copy of Cinema 4D to use your own likeness in your 3D scenes, or to drive the animation of other characters. The data can be deleted from your phone at all time.  

We may use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To present content from our services in an effective manner for you and for your computer or other device;

  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you;

  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;

  * If you pay for services using a credit card, we will transmit your credit card data to the appropriate credit card company and/or credit card payment processing company;

  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our services, when you choose to do so

  * To contact you about our services or products;

  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information or when we prompt you regarding a new use of information about you.

We will share your personal data with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell, trade, rent or disclose your information to others, except as provided herein:

  * We provide and support some of our services through contractual arrangements with service providers and other third parties. We and our service providers use your personal data to operate our web site and to deliver services. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for products and services purchased on our web site; and provide order information to third parties that help us deliver the services.

  * We will also disclose personal data in the following circumstances:

    * If it is required by law enforcement or judicial authorities, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation;

    * If we have a good faith belief that we are required or permitted to do so by law or legal process;

    * To protect our rights, reputation, property or the safety of us or others;

    * To defend or enforce our rights or your obligations;

    * If the disclosure is required by mandatory professional standards;

    * To a third party with your prior consent to do so; or

    * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to enforce or apply any contracts or agreement that may exist between you and us including this Privacy Policy, our Website Use Policy and our Terms of Service. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

  * In the event Maxon Computer, Inc. decides to sell all or part of its stock or assets or enter into a merger, we reserve the right to include your data, including personal data, among the assets transferred to the acquiring or surviving company.

We offer settings to control and manage the personal data we have about you, including the ability to:

  * Delete Data: You can ask us to erase or delete all or some of your personal data (e.g., if it is no longer necessary to provide Services to you).

  * Amend or Rectify Data: You can edit some of your personal data through your account. You can also ask us to amend your data in certain cases, particularly if it is inaccurate.

  * Object to, or Limit or Restrict, Use of Data: You can ask us to stop using all or some of your personal data (e.g., if we have no legal right to keep using it) or to limit our use of it (e.g., if your personal data is inaccurate or unlawfully held).

  * Right to Access and/or Take Your Data: You can ask us for a copy of your personal data.

  * You may change your personal data associated with your account on your “Member Settings” tab.

  * You may also access, request deletion, and correct your personal data by submitting a data request to [[info@cineversity.com](mailto:info@cineversity.com)](mailto:info@cineversity.com).

You may choose to let your membership or subscription lapse, in which case we will retain your information for a reasonable period of time in case you choose to re-subscribe. You may choose to completely remove your account in which case we will delete your information, including your learning history, within 60 days of your request. However, we may retain your personal data even after you have closed your account if reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations (including law enforcement requests), comply with contractual obligations, meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, maintain security, prevent fraud and abuse, enforce our Terms of Service or Website Use Policy, or fulfill your request to “unsubscribe” from further messages from us. We will retain de-personalized information after your account has been closed. You can request the removal of your account information by contacting us [info@cineversity.com](mailto:info@cineversity.com).

If you would like to access the information that we have about your use of and access to Cineversity.com services, please contact us at [info@cineversity.com](mailto:info@cineversity.com)

You can access some of the information that we collect about you. For example, by logging into your account, you can access information regarding certain personal data we maintain about you, your communication preferences and your payment settings.

With respect to your communications preferences, you can unsubscribe from newsletters by following the instructions included in the newsletter you receive, or you can log into your account and update your newsletter and email subscription options. Occasionally we may send out emails concerning website disruptions.

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you may be able to choose to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies some parts of our website may not work properly in your case.

We will only collect and process personal data about you where we have lawful basis. Lawful basis include consent (where you have given consent), contract (where processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you (e.g., to deliver the services you have requested) and “legitimate interests.”

Where we rely on your consent to process personal data, you have the right to withdraw or decline your consent at any time and where we rely on legitimate interests, you have the right to object. If you reside in the Designated Countries and have any questions about the lawful basis upon which we collect and use your personal data, please contact us at [info@cineversity.com](mailto:info@cineversity.com).

For certain services, we collect information under the direction of our clients (e.g., an entity that subscribes to the services for use by the entity’s personnel). In this respect, we act as a data processor under applicable laws. We will retain and use this personal data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and fulfill our obligations under those agreements with the data controllers. In these cases, the data controller will have its own privacy policy that applies to your data, including personal data. We encourage you to read their privacy policies to learn more about their data practices.

Access by you to your account is available through a user name (email) and  a password defined by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone, that you change your password often using a combination of letters and numbers, and that you ensure you use a secure web browser. We cannot be held accountable for activity that results from your own neglect to safeguard the secrecy of your password and username. If you share a computer with anyone, you should always log out of your account after you are finished in order to prevent access to your information from subsequent users of that computer.

Please notify Customer Support as soon as possible if your username or password is compromised.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal data, you acknowledge:

  * There are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control;

  * The security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this web site cannot be guaranteed and we shall have no liability to you or any third party for loss, misuse, disclosure or alteration of such information; and

  * Any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personal data in our control may have been compromised, we will try to notify you. To the extent you have provided us with your email address, we may notify you by email and you agree to our use of email as a means of such notification.

When you use our website, we may use cookies and other technologies in order to facilitate and customize your use of our services for the best possible experience. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the web site again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store unique identifiers, user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some web site features or services may not function properly without cookies. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences and video viewing activity. We use persistent, session, and flash cookies, and may use other types of cookies in the future.

Google Analytics uses “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of [http://www.cineversity.com](http://www.cineversity.com/) (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to understand the services that you use and how you use them. Any information collected from you, including personal data, is anonymous and unlinked. For more information about Google Analytics, including Google’s privacy policy, please visit: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html>.

We currently do not share personal data with third parties for their direct marketing purposes without your permission.

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page (with a notice that the Privacy Policy has been updated on the website). You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our web site and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

Your continued use of the Services after such modifications will constitute your agreement to the updated terms of the modified Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy or otherwise need to contact us, please call at 805-376-3333 or email at [info@cineversity.com](mailto:info@cineversity.com). You may also contact us by mail at the following address:

Maxon Computer, Inc.

2640 Lavery Court, Suite A

Newbury Park, CA 91320
